Contact

pardhu.charan@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/krishnacharan-a3721218 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Data Science
Deep Learning
Machine Learning

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Telugu (Native or Bilingual)

Krishna Charan

Machine Learning Engineer and Data Scientist Hyderabad

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer networking industry. Skilled in Data Science, Python (Programming Language), Natural Language Processing (NLP), Deep Learning, and Machine Learning. Strong engineering professional with a Master's degree focused in Artificial Intelligence from University of Hyderabad.

Experience

Persistent Systems
Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Data Scientist
November 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)
Hyderabad Area, India

ADP

4 years 5 months

Senior Software Development Engineer April 2016 - Present (4 years 5 months) Hyderabad Area, India

Senior Software Engineer April 2016 - November 2018 (2 years 8 months) Hyderabad Area, India

Ains Inc Software Developer August 2013 - Present (7 years 1 month)

AINS, Inc.
Software Developer
August 2013 - Present (7 years 1 month)

Developer of Crystal Reports and windows tools and Web developer.

Education

University of Hyderabad

Master's degree, Artificial Intelligence · (2011 - 2013)

VR SIDDHARTHA ENGINEERING COLLEGE

Computer Science · (2007 - 2011)